If you are not into crafting or special effects makeup or just like me a lazy person
Then I have the best easy and fast Halloween costumes for you. Thanks to devil walking
I will show you four outfits today and they all consist of only one piece
So it's really fast and easy to dress them and they're comfy
Let's just get started right away and I will change into the first one first one and I think this is
without trying them my favorite if I still have that opinion at the end of
the video but yeah this is the blood splatter suit and I paired it with red
heels and I can also like use this clutch to go with it so one suit one
accessory and heels and you have a complete outfit and I can tell you it's
really comfy the fabric is really really stretchy there is this keyhole cut out here in the front
which I think makes the girls look really really nice and throughout the whole suit there is this
contouring and shading so shading is better I think we have the lighter parts like for example
here and here and the darker parts at the outer sides of the legs and body to
give this contour effect and make an optical slimmer illusion like what you
do with your face when you contour it. With this flattered theme I think this is a
really cute outfit I don't know does it make me a psychopath to think that this
is cute and what we can also try is see how this looks with black light what do
you think I think it looks way whiter than before let me just check in the mirror
and the red doesn't look as bloody anymore but I think it's a cool effect
and I really like it now the white really pops whereas without the black
light it's more of a muddy white in places but I think it's really cool.
Now if you want to go the extra mile for Halloween you could add some splatter to
your face as well with some face paint or body paint and just a toothbrush and
then splatter it on or use a brush to do some really big ones. That is just a
thought but I think this is also already a great one and now something I've been looking forward
to is this dress I'm in love with this dress because it's just so beautiful and I feel so
ladylike with the cut and also the sleeves and all the flowers I paired it with a
big ass joker and some PVC shiny heels as well as with PVC underwear so you can see that through a
bit and I actually have the perfect bag for it since it's Diaz de los Muertos themed. I have my
skull bag here which is a great accessory for this kind of outfit. Now I do have my skull with me
I just think it looks so good and it suits me.
Just the perfect outfit and I am honest I would not only wear this for Halloween because
it's just such a nice dress.
Especially if you think like summertime since it's mesh fabric you can throw it over a bikini
for beach party as well. Who would have thought?
Some additional effort for Halloween could be that you can make a
headpiece with flowers, with roses, could be artificial roses
to upgrade this outfit a bit but I'm happy as it is.
And now I will change into the next one.
Outfit number three and it's giving slimy
alien H.R. Giger vibes.
So the color palette is a bit unusual with the purple. You could do purple makeup for example. We again have the nice shading here, body contouring and I also love the back because now I have a spine. I think it's a really cool print here. And it was actually really hard for me to come up with an accessory for this one. But I found something.
So if we're talking about slimy, I have a tentacle.
Tentacle?
Is it tentacle?
Is it tentacle or tentacle?
In German it's tentacle.
So yeah, I think that is a fitting accessory.
I feel like I'm holding a baby.
But it's way more fun.
It's not color matched with the suit but with my hair.
So yeah, I think that's a nice one.
It's actually quite heavy.
And of course you could add some slime.
Why not?
Or you could wear this outfit if you're invited to a space model party.
Or, I don't know, an alien model party.
This is just so fun to play with.
This is the only outfit for today with a front zip.
So the first one had a back zip.
It doesn't dress in none at all.
And now we have a front zip so you can open that.
it does ruin the design a bit so it's not as yeah close anymore obviously but I like this one too
thank you still the same for this one I turned the black light on again because
it is such an amazing effect it looks now like white white suit with a bit of red
So definitely something to wear for a party with black lights.
For the shoes I chose these plateau heels this time and the holographic parts sometimes
look like purple so that was the closest I could find to purple shoes.
Anyway I do have a last catsuit and I'm going to change now.
I was just wondering what I still got in this handbag because I haven't used it in ages.
tissues, a concealer and hair ties if you want to know. Anyway this is the last outfit for today.
It is a mesh catsuit and the mesh is tight but also really stretchy and what I love about the
devil walking suits is that they're really long so I can actually use the thumb holes here without
it hurting my hands and my fingers and without it being too short and also the whole
suit is really long enough and stretchy enough so that I can wear it perfectly comfortable
perfectly comfortable that's all that's strange anyway I am once again wearing the pvc underwear
and I decided to leave the zipper a bit more open so that you can actually see it
which matches with my cute kitty handbag and the shoes so again easy halloween outfit
quick and easy all four of them all four really comfy and i think this is more like old school
pattern um cow webs cow webs is it cow webs yeah i think so spider web spider web what
if it's a spiderweb what is it how web then is it the same does it would even exist i don't know
it's way too late for these kind of thoughts yeah once again turning around and now
uh closing the zipper for you so that you can see it i actually lied the outfit before i said
this is the only one with the front zip and it wasn't i just didn't realize in that moment and
already forgotten about this one anyway I think I prefer the open version and as for my favorite
outfit for today I can also like close it from here and um but I actually like the
four open one my favorite outfit today was this one actually the mesh dress because I felt so
really good in it and I thought it really suited me. It made a great body shape so yeah.
Also it's not my 12 millionth catsuit so it was something new which I actually liked.
So yeah. But you can tell me in the comments which one you prefer and you can also check
out the Devil Walking homepage and use my code if you want to order there. You can upload
the Halloween outfit photos with devil walking suits on social media and I'm happy to see how
you style them. I think for this one if you want to upgrade this one you can add some fake spider
webs to your hair maybe or draw one in your face. So yeah but I think that's it for today.
I will leave you to it and I hope I can see you in the next video. I do have another devil walking
video by the way so if you want to see more of these awesome printed catsuits
then check out the other videos and yeah have a nice day see you around bye